## Non Doe

Email: nonjirawat2506@gmail.com Phone: 21/483 Ramkhamhaeng Road Bangkok 10240 ,Thailand nonjirawat2506@gmail.com I am interested in software engineering and full-stack web application development. Additionally, I am determined to use the knowledge I have gained through practice and learning, and to be patient with myself, in order to develop into a professional. APPLICATIONS DEVELOPER November-March ,2022-2023 I collaborated with a team to develop a web application using the Go programming language and the React framework. I implemented database models using SQLite and utilized tools like GitHub. July to present As a Web Developer at Suranaree University of Technology in Nakhon Ratchasima, Thailand, in 2023, I developing a program for job search applications. I applied Bootstrap 5, Node.js, and Express, along with JavaScript. Additionally, I have designed database models using MySQL and utilized code tools such as GitHub and Visual Studio Code. Thai: Native language English: Good Bachelor's degree o Front-End Developer I am a front-end developer with more than 3 years of experience writing

Front-End Developer I am a front-end developer with more than 3 years of experience writing html, css, and js. I'm motivated, result-focused and seeking a successful team-oriented company with opportunity to grow.

Experience

KlowdBox

San Fr, CA

Jan 2011 - Feb 2015

Fr developer

did This and that

Akount

San Monica, CA

Jan 2011 - Feb 2015

Fr developer

did This and that

Education

Sample Institute of technology

San Fr, CA

Jan 2011 - Feb 2015

Fr developer

did This and that

Akount

San Monica, CA

Jan 2011 - Feb 2015

Fr developer

did This and that

**Projects** 

**DSP** 

I am a front-end developer with more than 3 years of experience writing html, css, and js. I'm motivated, result-focused and seeking a successful team-oriented company with opportunity to grow.

**DSP** 

I am a front-end developer with more than 3 years of experience writing html, css, and js. I'm motivated, result-focused and seeking a successful team-oriented company with opportunity to grow. <u>link</u>

Skills	
Javascript	
<b>✓</b> ✓ □ □	
CSS	
<b>✓ ✓</b> □ □	

Interests

Football, programming.